Oh
I almost said a bad word
I
Is
Oh
I
Didn't even say three to one good luck
Simon to remember this guy the agent's he
He scares me the whole atmosphere is changed. It really is how are you?
Oh
It's not here for the chat
We go
Scary
He is really scary
Yes
Come on
Look, this is how I imagine his day of reckoning as he's led through the gates of hell
Gracious self-signment
Oh, don't put that over his nose
Sir
Fire is gasoline
Oh
Do not try this at all. They're not gonna run except fun
This is just a thrill
Oh my gosh
Oh
My getting early finish of this goes wrong
Oh my gosh
Oh
Not a joke
It's killing time
How would you do?
He said your head on fire
Did you make all the heat?
I didn't know it'd bloody lighter fuel
It was scary was it was yeah and as much as I don't really want you to have to go through that again
It was massively entertaining and horrific all at once
With the amount of product that's in that hair that was a risk
You're a very brave man to do that you thought I had to come up a rescue of one point
And that very good very good
Now I was really captivated by Alicia's while we were running with a bucket
I mean
So I praise you for that. I really never seen anything like it
I'm gonna say yes
Bruno oh, I'm gonna say yes
I'm saying yes
So some talent or not I like it well
Oh
Whoa
ALAN
ALA
RIVってる
I don't know, I don't know.
Let's go.
Let's go!
Whoa!
Yeah!
Oh!
Oh, my God.
Yes!
Ah
Turn all right
Hmm
One in the
I love it, I love it.
I'm very careful of sleeping.
Up here?
Up.
Okay.
It's worth climbing with the eye, the language.
Are you ready?
Yeah!
I'm ready!
Why are you going to touch me?
God, I can't believe you.
With the eyes!
I mean, I can't.
I can't believe you.
I'm going to see you in the first row.
I was looking at you and you didn't look at me like this.
You didn't look at me like this.
I'm so tired.
One more.
Oh, I'm not a younger boy.
Yeah, yeah.
No!
Yes!
Yeah.
We will fall in danger in the hands of the world.
Morning, scary act.
I don't like it.
Between the dark and the light.
The gods and evil.
Which for you choose?
Oh, dear.
No.
I'm not.
Oh, no.
No, they're done.
Oh, no. They're coming out.
No, I don't know.
No, you can't.
Don't come down here.
Careful, Simon.
There are two pathways for you, David.
Yes.
Which do you choose?
Take an apple.
Take a bite.
It's nice.
Hmm.
Your turn, Alicia.
Between the gods and evil.
Which for you choose?
Take an apple.
Bite if you bite.
It's something I've got to tell you.
But it can wait.
It can wait.
Amanda, stand up.
Oh, God, just always be.
Your hands out.
Face up.
Don't close that.
There we are.
Your destiny will be chosen by another.
Oh, God.
Between the dark and the light.
Only choose.
Left or right.
Now, ta!
Right.
Here's right, though.
Right, right.
Take a bite.
Amanda.
You know why they say the beauties on your skin deep.
Because we're all rotten to the core.
EHHHH Metroid Isid 행복.
It's stuck to the inic.
oder you can't take.
No, no, no.
No, I'm not.
How am I going to like it?
How could that be horrible?
Okay, well, that was horrific.
Oh, I can't.
The witch has turned into a cockroach.
So we're going to have to talk to them.
I mean, I was scared to death.
I mean, I'd quite like to see what else was going to happen in the future.
Alicia, what do you think?
I thought the act was actually brilliant.
Uh, David, I thought I thought he was stunning.
So I think we should vote and let me kick this off with a yes!
I'm saying yes!
Amanda, it's a yes from me.
We want to see you in the next round.
I don't know how you did that.
Maybe we'll see you in the finals.
Congratulations.
He was a very chewy.
I think she was quite a good one.
Hello.
Okay, what's your name, please?
Good luck.
Whatever you are.
Very mysterious.
I know.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, it's a song, not a thing.
I don't know what he's going to do,
but it involves a sword,
so you shouldn't try this at home.
Okay.
Actually, I have a lot of flashes.
We'll read it.
No, don't do that.
Oh, no, no.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my goodness.
What's the what now?
It's got more than I.
Oh, my God, normal.
Oh, listen.
I'm always going to do all three,
he's not.
Oh, no, oh, my God.
Oh, God, it's like a hat trick.
Oh, my God.
No!
Oh, no way.
Oh, my God.
That's insane.
What's he doing?
He's not. He's not.
He's not.
Oh, no, don't do that.
Woo!
Oh!
Oh, my God.
Come on, you're in.
I don't know that I don't know when I lost my mind.
Oh, no.
What's he going to do now?
He's never something so passing about the place.
Why is he looking at you?
No, no, no, no, don't love me.
Oh, my God.
I've never seen anything like this before.
I think my house can't do that.
Oh, my goodness.
Oh, my God, I'm sick.
Oh, my God.
Paul, I'm waiting. Who get man?
Paul, I'm calling.
Oh, my God.
Oh.
What is that, I've lost.
Someone stop it, man.
Oh, my God.
What's their magic with you?
Ha, ha, ha.
I do it for you.
Oh, my God.
Wait a minute.
Oh, my.
What do you say, man?
What they doing?
Mm-hmm.
Scary.
Oh, my God.
Oh, I'm getting scared.
Yeah!
Woo!
Ah!
Look at all of me now.
Woo!
Yay!
we want
Wife and face by Samsung
guys every time you die
but you be there
While we count
谢谢
Oh
I can't watch it I can't watch it already I can't watch it
You don't like these deer no makes me born
Oh
Simon you must be happy because I know you love clowns
You find you gonna be okay
You alright coming soon next
Oh
Hey
And I need
I'll take you
Can you go in?
Oh, baby, baby
You can't see me now
You will never see me now
So I am in prison
But I can't watch you here
Or over here
Right now
I'm standing right in front of one of the gadgets
No!
What?
Did you touch that?
I don't know what's going on
A man, please follow me up onto the stage
Oh, baby, yeah
I can't take a seat
I don't like it
I'm just going to grab something from over here
A man, please hold the balloon by the stick
The balloons are the first thing that we all learn to lose
Like the child that lost this balloon earlier today
They thought it was a gust of wind
It wasn't, it was me
I stood to take a lesson
And lost
You might think it was rather mean to burst a balloon like that
But losing things is an important part of life
I'll show you what I mean
The man who the box on this truck is the theatre's most property box
Please open the lid
Without showing anyone the lender
You will take one of the items
You place it under the cloth of the collar
Being invisible means I can't have material possessions if I own
So instead, I just see you moving from other people
And, blessedly yet, I can come down on the feet to do my vision
And you shall reach in with your right hand
Take a random object and hold it so no one can see you with a cross
You'll hold it a seat in your hands
One of them nobody wants to be known
In that moment, you could have taken anything from that box and yet
A man who knows exactly what you have taken
Sure
A man who I want you to take a deep breath
Until everyone what unleashes is holding in her mind to have
A dummy
No way
This is weird
But this just won the object left to identify
The one that you took at the beginning of matter
There is a piece of chalk on the troll
Please pick it up and bring it to me over here
I'm sending it over to my boy
And let go of it, Melda
I will take it from here
What is it doing up?
A man who please lift the path and show everyone what you put there
Please keep hold of those keys and take them back to your seat
You see, I've been amongst you these last three days
It's just no one ever saw me
That might house kids
Are they?
Amanda, those thieves that you remember me chose belong to David
What?
And David, please look after him because next time I won't be so kind
Goodbye until I see you all again
Hello, hello, hello
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen
We are tonight's entertainment
Full fight now
I like that
Wow
Ha ha
Ha ha ha ha
Have a sleep and sleep too loud, hug me out
Everybody talking, trying to see me
Just believe they hate, breathing, even six feet deep
But you're saying, hold up, let's go
You need me, baby, hold up, let's go
You need me, baby, hold up, let me go
You need me, baby, hold it down
Now you've talked about 10 of my fellas
It's the sound of your career in my
Whatever doesn't kill you
Simple makes you a stranger
I belong with the animal cages
What are you doing?
When you don't need a face, look, come on, act for friendship
Come pick up my hand
I'm gonna do it
Bassline hits, I'm on hitline
There's no idea where I'm going
Then I'm finding a chick, I can make my...
I'm not missing a mouse
It's a sweet pop in the dark
To the ocean, I'm a shabby
I'm a shabby, I'm a dog in the rock
We pop in this
Slated Rolex and the Grammy Awards
They steal selling dope
That's those Miami boys
Killers everywhere, they know place to run
Forgive me for my...
Oh my god
Ain't no mercy, I ain't no mercy
I ain't no mercy
Got that purple-numbered demon like you
Rose, hey
Oh my god
I'm a little bit dangerous
Hello
What is your name?
My name is Sydney Abbott
Sydney, how old are you?
Ten
Ten years old? Wow!
And what do you do, Sydney?
I'm gonna be dancing for you tonight
Well, you are just so sweet
And so small that I just absolutely wish you the best
Good luck
Thank you so much, bye!
Okay, okay, goodbye
Thank you for voting on cuteness
Oh my goodness
Does she not know that she was supposed to stay in perform?
Oh!
Oh
Excuse me
What?
Wow
Oh my goodness
Oh my gosh
What was that?
Did you see that?
It was weird, just there
Welcome
What's your name, please?
Elizabeth
Just Elizabeth
Why have you come on Britain's got talent?
Because I want to show you something special
And try and make the impossible possible
Wow
The stage is yours Elizabeth
Theaters of London's West End
It's said to be haunted by many ghosts
In 1919
The great Harry Houdini appeared on stage
And offered a large cash sum
For anyone who could prove the existence of them
Amanda, I'd like you to take this journal in your left hand
And I'd like you to come with me
I'm scared
Legends have said
That spirits departed
Walked the halls and stores
Of the Theaters of London
It is said to be good luck to see ghosts for a performer
For others
Not so much
Looks scared
Oh my god
Where are we going?
That's something that's dead
Amanda, please take a seat
These photographs are of people
Who have lived and died over 100 years ago
I'm kind of creeped out
Can you hold out your left hand like this?
Now in a moment
I want you to count these photographs face down onto the table
One at a time
When you place them down
You're going to feel a connection to one
When you feel that connection
I want you to stop
And to place that photograph face down into this cigar box
Look at the photographs each and every one is different
But you were drawn to one and you don't know why
No
Open the cigar box and take out the photograph that you chose
Turn it over and read out what it says
Agatha Turner 1860
Before this all began
I gave you a journal that's over 100 years old
Open the page I've bookmarked
And read out the paragraph that I've circled in red
Miss Turner was born in the 1800s
She loved visiting the West End to be entertained
She tragically died in 1860
And her ghost
Is said to haunt the theaters that she once loved
Amanda
This moment was always meant to be
Look over your left shoulder
Oh my god
Someone's a good home
Oh, you're up
Oh my god
Go
This is just switch back to home
I thought it was gonna stop
Hello, good evening
What should I am pleased?
My name is Marcel, I'm 35 years old
Okay
And what should normal job?
My normal job is being a fantasy illusionist
Okay, we'll listen best of luck
Because I don't want to ask any more questions
Cool, let's do it
Okay
Do it
Oh my god
All that house that's happening
That's not here
What's going?
Oh my god
Don't go to cage
Look at cage
Oh my god
Here is, he's not in cage
Hey, light
Oh my god
We let him go, he's within the tossed,
Despite him wet off,
Brushed hard,
Oh my
See you around the back.
With your pick, here we go.
You strike your right back
!!!
Come on, Lark!
Oh my God!
Oh my god!
Oh my god.
Hello!
Ahhhhhh
WhERO
Wow! lots of Οdam gods
Oh!
Well, that was utterly terrifying and thrilling,
and one of the most extraordinary things
we've ever seen on Brent's Got Talent.
Well, now we know why you are called the Freaks,
because that was just out of this world.
I mean, she was a human skipping work.
Oh, no!
I've never seen that before ever.
There was something everywhere.
I mean, it was such a feast for the eyes, so dangerous.
You are so brave, and your parents are even braver.
It was just, honestly, out of this world brilliant.
You're not a war.
You're from the opening, the graphics, the idea, the imagination,
the creativity, the skill, and it was faultless.
I have one question.
Who's idea was this?
What's your name, sir?
Aussie.
Aussie, you're a genius.
You really are.
I'm one with your imagination.
You should be very proud.
Good for you.
I have a feeling I know where this is going.
David?
I am going to say yes.
Is he yes for me?
Absolutely.
For gigantic, yes, is.
So long, you've been.
Oh, you've been.
Yes.
Yes!
Please be done.
Oh.
Oh, no.
What's he doing now?
He can't be worse than what he just did.
I hope not.
Oh, no.
Yes!
What's he going to do?
I don't know.
Man, you're scared, man.
Stop, stop, stop, stop!
Oh.
What do you think of him?
It's amazing.
It's crazy.
It's dangerous.
It's wrong.
You should change your name to Shishka Bob.
Fighting.
Are you okay?
Sophia.
I have mixed feelings.
This is very disturbing and fun at the same time.
I like you and I don't like you at the same time.
I love that.
Because we've seen this kind of app before.
The stuff I've seen before, like this, is tame in comparison.
In my opinion.
If anything, the app is too short.
We're going to vote.
Howie, yes or no?
It's yes for me.
It's crazy.
I don't want to see you again and I can't wait.
Yes.
You've got four yeses.
We'll see you again.
I'm sorry.
Me.
**
He looks like Paula, we love the difference in their number.
Every start of the day is always learning
Does that mean the manager will get tired of having to be seven months?
Yes, he was gonna be pretty hard of course
But love not that hard
I mean that'm gonna be funny
Lovena we're happy for you
Correct?
Yes, Jie
If you just want to subscribe
All right
La pediatrician is here on Wednesday.
Someone is right there in the past,
already at the Station,
not in the right street.
From Anneli neither in the back,
nor in the town,
nor in the UI,
neither moving towards the ceiling,
Go back, go back!
Go back!
No, no, go back!
It is very, it is most...
almost full of underneath.
Moro!
Go back!
It's amazing to see it in comparison to it.
Great jobli on this!
Go!
Comeportally!
Wait!
Oh
It's so huge!
Ah!
Well done.
Wow, I'm going to Dragon Blue and the last one cool guy forever.
Don't let organizes get so control lines
I
Will you
You
漂亮
Yeah
Pull top it says
Let's go
How real
What is quite scary
Oh